It’s for students that are in the art clubs or in Art 11/12, or in Art 8/9.
このイベントでは、美術部や美術を選択している中学2～高3の生徒の作品を展示しています。
So, in their art classes they make a lot of projects and then they get to put their work up.
アートクラスでは、色々なプロジェクトを行い、作品を仕上げていきます。
They get to put their work up and display their best work.
その様な中から、最高の作品を展示しています。
They get to choose what their best work is
生徒個人が、どの作品を展示するかを決め
and then every student gets a chance to put their work in the show and show it off
すべての生徒が自分の作品を展示をする事ができます。
Students take a foundations course
基礎コースを選択している生徒は
and that means that they get to do sculpture, they do ceramic,
彫刻、陶芸をはじめ、
they do painting, they do collage, they do drawing techniques.
絵画やコラージュ作成など、描写の技術を学びます。
So basically, there’s everything through all those disciplines
生徒たちは、その様な基本的な技術を習得し、
and they get to show what their best work was in those projects.
自分たちが行ったプロジェクトの中で、最高な作品を発表しています。
There’s things like masks for “Day of the Dead”
例えば、「死者の日」というメキシコの伝統的なお祭りで使われる
and all my students took part in those masks.
マスク（お面）があります。私のすべての生徒はこのマスクを作成しました。
Some students did mosaics,
その他の生徒は、モザイクを作ったり
we did a bunch of still life
沢山の生徒が静物画を描きました。
and then some students went on field trips
また、他の生徒たちはフィールドトリップにも参加しました。
so what’s behind me right here is from a field trip to the Vancouver Art Gallery
私の後ろにある作品は、バンクーバー・アートギャラリーに行った際の作品です。
and they went to an Emily Carr exhibit and then did a workshop
エミリーカー（大学）へも訪問し、ワークショップも受けました。
Mashu Higa, actually he is in the North Shore News this week for his art
生徒の一人、Higa Mashu君（日本）の作品は、今週、ノースショアニュース（地元紙）で、取り上げられました。
And he is creating a work on “crowd-sourcing”.
彼の作品は、「クラウド（群衆）・ソーシング（参加）」というコンセプトを使っています。
Getting people together to participate in his art.
色々な人達を彼の作品に参加させています。
They are putting a pin where they live in the world, where they come from
参加する人達は、自分たちが世界のどこから来たか、どこに住んでいるか、
and then on the piece that he created he drew a piece of himself,
ピンを彼の作品につけます。その作品に今度は、
kind of like a self-portrait
彼の等身大の絵を描きます。
there putting pins where they live or come from and then they are writing a comment
その後、みんながそれぞれ、
about where they come or about Canada on the piece,
どこから来た、カナダの事に関してのコメントを書き加えました。
so they get to actually participate in the piece which is really neat
Mashuの作品は、みんなが参加して完成した素敵な作品となりました。
Mashu’s work is actually part of his application for Emily Carr,
Mashuはこの作品を、エミリーカー大学受験に使用する予定です。
They get you to do a project, so this is for him to get to work on his application
美術を選択した生徒は、色々なプロジェクトに取り組みます。その為、クラスを
While he is actually in art class
受講している間に、大学受験に必要な作品も作っていくことが出来るです。